[Music]
car 67 come in car 67 this is car 67
this is car 67 code code five nothing to
report we've got nothing to
[Music]
report you are such an idiot man I mean
van Hagar had just as many hits as the
original Van Halen okay 5150 Best of
Both Worlds when it's love dreams summer
nights finish what you started black and
blue right now right now now really
you're going to come at me with right
now please what are you talking about
right now was the theme of the entire
generation it was a Pepsi jingle you
mental Cas you not listened to the
Poetry The Genius of Samy hegar's lyrics
talking about living for the day taking
advantage of what you have right now
don't wait till tomorrow with Teresa
Teresa did you just say Teresa no holy
you just put your ex-wife into a
van I did not oh my God no I didn't hey
guys you got no I didn't here by the no
I didn't no don't all the guys over tell
the guys to mind their own business you
mind your own business Hawk you leave
you leave you leave Samy stop it you
stop it right next to me stop it you
stop it die in a car fire you jackass
stop do
do so something bugging you or yeah
something's bugging me you don't talk
about right now I'm going to
this
car hey it's Captain Ed Captain
education this car it's as easy as
one
two
three oh yeah that's good why is
Sergeant Pepper humping our car come on
there's no way you don't know who that
is he's got this great show for kids
that makes learning fun and hip he's
great Captain Ed drink my piss car ah
classic Captain Ed this is our car
all right I don't care how many
kids he's educated taking this guy
in come on he's just goofing around
typical Hollywood he thinks
just cuz he's a celebrity he can do
whatever he wants he can my wife
and I'm just going to stand around and
take it get over here excuse me sir big
fan could I trouble you for some ID
please why you need to see some ID huh
you obviously know who he is Fanboy well
I doubt his real name is Captain
education oh wow it's really Captain
education yeah it legally changed can
you even change your name to Captain
legally no I I actually am a captain
you two want to get married I can do it
all we got to do is find an ocean you
and I should have an underwear
party on man why did you do that he
rushed me it's just his way he's a goofy
guy and he uses that goofiness to fight
illiteracy so just give him a break he's
just having a bad day I'm having the
best
day seriously typical Hollywood
celebrity does whatever he wants puke on
my shoe no problem make a mistake it's
okay live your life with no
responsibilities right Captain you are
an idol to children for God's sakes
that's true my kids really look up to
him he's their hero I'm not but uh they
love him doesn't that piss you off you
spent your whole life trying to be a
good cop and this Hollywood Fly by Night
can do whatever he wants he's worshiped
like a god I mean you're getting shot at
and he's taking my wife out to dinner
and doing the hibbity dibbity okay I
feel like I need to make sure you know
Captain Ed is isn't the weatherman your
wife left you for uh ex-wife and yes I
know I'm not some kind of that
dick I'm to make you feel like a special
boy H wow it's been a while since
anyone's made me feel special but um I'm
going to have to decline I'm married uh
I got a gun in here somewhere no way
does he have a gun I'm pretty sure it's
there it is I was wrong come
on okay so we definitely have to take
this guy in gee do you think so yes
normally I wouldn't ask and I know it's
not procedure but do you think we can
get a picture with Captain Ed it would
go a long way with the kids you want to
take a picture with him seriously yes
you know come to think of it if my wife
wants to screw me over by a
weatherman I'll get revenge on her by
a kid show host yeah that makes
sense okay let's okay let's take a like
a selfie it's actually called an usie
really yeah like if there's more than
one person it's called an see now okay
okay uh cheese that's good that's real
good now hey pretend you're an urban
youth okay and and and he's teaching you
how to read okay cheese all right now
get back to no no let me teabag him no
Captain Ed Captain
Ed what's wrong with him he's not
breathing he's not breathing Captain
head captain head wake him up no come on
God wake up he's not waking up okay you
know he's beloved by millions right I
know he's beloved by mil GL if you die
my kids will hate me
please I got an idea I got an idea get
in the car just go go come on come on
come
[Music]
on you know right now really is a good
song is that Van Halen or van Hagar shut
[Music]
up